<theme>
	<formatVersion>4</formatVersion>

	<view name="system">
		<text name="info1" extra="true">
			<text>Ikemen GO is an open source fighting game engine that supports resources from the M.U.G.E.N engine, written in Google’s programming language, Go. It is a complete rewrite of a prior engine known simply as Ikemen.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="PT">
			<text>Ikemen GO é um motor de jogo de luta de código aberto que suporta recursos do motor M.U.G.E.N, escrito na linguagem de programação do Google, Go. É uma reescrita completa de um motor anterior conhecido simplesmente como Ikemen.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="EN">
			<text>Ikemen GO is an open source fighting game engine that supports resources from the M.U.G.E.N engine, written in Google’s programming language, Go. It is a complete rewrite of a prior engine known simply as Ikemen.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="ES">
			<text>Ikemen GO es un motor de juegos de lucha de código abierto que admite recursos del motor M.U.G.E.N., escrito en el lenguaje de programación Go de Google. Es una reescritura completa de un motor anterior conocido simplemente como Ikemen.</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="FR">
			<text>Ikemen GO est un moteur de jeu de combat open source qui utilise les ressources du moteur M.U.G.E.N. et est écrit en Go, le langage de programmation de Google. Il s'agit d'une réécriture complète d'un moteur précédent connu sous le nom d'Ikemen.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info1" extra="true" lang="DE">
			<text>Ikemen GO ist eine Open-Source-Engine für Kampfspiele, die Ressourcen der M.U.G.E.N-Engine unterstützt und in Googles Programmiersprache Go geschrieben ist. Es handelt sich um eine vollständige Neuentwicklung einer Vorgänger-Engine, die einfach Ikemen hieß.</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info2" extra="true">
			<text>Ikemen GO</text>
		</text>

				<text name="info3" extra="true">
			<text>2016</text>
		</text>

		<text name="info4" extra="true">
			<text>Ikemen GO</text>
		</text>
	</view>

	<customView name="HCoinSpin">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>


	<customView name="CoinOps Details">
      <image name="art3" extra="true">
         <path>./../assets/coinops/default.png</path>
         <zIndex>7</zIndex>
      </image>
	</customView>

</theme>
